So I'm on the AWS console.
Let me just search for translate.
And here we have Amazon translate.
And it says Amazon translate provides fast, affordable,
and quality translation for your multi-lingual needs.
So you can do a launch real-time translation.
And here you can see two options.
So you have batch translation.
And if I just click on this create job,
and I just give the name of a job.
And then I select source language.
So what is the language for my source text?
And I can select one of them, or I can also select auto.
And it will auto detect.
And then then I have the target language in which language
I want this text to be translated to.
And then I can upload my document in S3 bucket.
And I have to give the location of S3 bucket
and just give the format.
Whether it's HTML, Word, Document, Excel, and so on.
Then I also need to provide the location of S3 bucket
where the output data after the Amazon translate
has translated would be stored in.
And then you have customization options.
You can click on formality.
Whether you want the translation to be formal, informal.
You can also do profanity masking if you make like.
And then if I just go back to Amazon translate and click here.
And then if I do real-time translation,
it can be the text or document.
So source language, you can do auto detection,
or you can select one of the languages from the 75 languages.
Then you can select the target language here.
Let me just select the target language as maybe German.
And let me enter the text here.
We say-- and let me just say, welcome to my Udemy course.
And you can see it's translated in German.
So I'm not conversant with German.
So hopefully it is translated correctly.
And then you can choose some additional settings
like custom terminology, brevity, formality, profanity masking,
and so on.
So that's at a high level how Amazon translate works.
So hopefully we have gotten high level overview
of how Amazon translate works.
I'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you.